(Howard:)Sorry, just
passing through.
(Howard:)I think this fell off your cart.
(Raj:)Come on. What do you say?
(Raj:)Let me make it up to you.
(Isabella:)You're very persistent.
(Raj:)It's my one move.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Isabella:)This Sunday night,
you may take me to dinner
(Isabella:)at a nice restaurant.
(Penny:)Great.
Where would you like to go?
(Isabella:)Your choice.
(Isabella:)It can be Pakistani food,
if you like.
(Raj:)Excuse me, but I'm Indian.
(Isabella:)And now you know how it feels.
(Penny:)So, were you turned
on even a little bit?
(Amy:)It was like
(Amy:)being hit on
by Rat Pack Pee-wee Herman.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, is that a yes?
No!
(Scene:)Amy,
(Sheldon:)I didn't want it
to come to this.